<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Michiel Tukker</title>
    <link>https://MichielTukker.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Michiel Tukker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 22:01:22 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://MichielTukker.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fedora</title>
      <link>https://MichielTukker.github.io/2020/05/fedora/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 22:01:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MichielTukker.github.io/2020/05/fedora/</guid>
      <description>Switching to Fedora 32 So I switched to Fedora 32 last week, after getting annoyed with Ubuntu 20.04 pushing snap-packages everywhere. Fedora has been a delight, although I&amp;rsquo;ve had several small hickups. I don&amp;rsquo;t blame Fedora for this, the problem is that I&amp;rsquo;ve grown accustomed to the ease of use of Ubuntu or Windows at the cost of using non-free software. Fedora ships only open source / free software in their standard package repositories which I think is a good thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://MichielTukker.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 15:40:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MichielTukker.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About me I&amp;rsquo;m Michiel Tukker, an engineer and software developer.
Comment policy The comment policy is simple:
 Be polite – don’t be rude to anyone and respect others. If something you would say would get you bottled on the head offline, please don’t say it here. Remember there is a person behind the screen and that your words affect people. Don’t troll. We appreciate and welcome criticism towards writers here, but comments that add no value to the discussion or that are merely insulting would be deleted without exception.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://MichielTukker.github.io/2020/04/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 15:19:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MichielTukker.github.io/2020/04/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my new website This is the first post on my new website using Hugo. Everything appears to work now. I&amp;rsquo;ve set this up as a static site, so I don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about the latest php exploit or other vulnerabilities.
How it works The site is powered by Hugo, a static site generator. The content of the site is written in markdown and stored in a git repository.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
